Guide to the Duke Management Company records, 1980-1993
Duke University. University Archives
Duke Management Company records 1980-1993
Duke University. University Archives
Duke Management Company (DUMAC)
19.5 linear feet Extent: 19,000 items
In 1989, Duke University's Board of Trustees approved the formation of Duke Management Company (DUMAC) as a separate, non-profit support corporation of Duke University. DUMAC recommends investment policy and strategy, seeks and analyzes specific opportunities, and manages ongoing operations and activities. DUMAC operates under a cascading delegation of authority from the Board of Trustees and the DUMAC Board of Directors. Records include materials pertaining to Chief Executive Officer Eugene McDonald's office, including minutes, memoranda outlining proposed agendas, reports on past meetings, draft resolutions, studies, correspondence; staff meetings and memoranda; and long-range planning initiatives. Other major subjects in the collection include investment, athletics, information technology/computing reorganization, land resources, internal audits, policies, budget forecasts, and compensation. A significant part of the collection (found in boxes 3 and 4) includes materials related to discussion in the late 1980s about possible commercial use for part of Duke Forest.
UA.16.01.0001
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
Provenance
The materials were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1992 and 1993.
Historical Note
In 1989, Duke University's Board of Trustees approved the formation of Duke Management Company (DUMAC) as a separate, non-profit support corporation of Duke University. Solely responsible for managing the University's investment assets, DUMAC operates under a cascading delegation of authority from the Board of Trustees and the DUMAC Board of Directors. DUMAC recommends investment policy and strategy, seeks and analyzes specific opportunities, and manages ongoing operations and activities. Located in nearby off-campus facilities, the professional staff is organized around functional investment areas of public investments, hedged strategies, private investments, and operations/administration. The CEO of DUMAC from its inception until 2000 was Eugene McDonald. During the period these boxes cover, McDonald was also Senior Vice President and University Counsel at Duke; the boxes in this collection therefore also contain papers related to the duties of those offices.
Collection Overview
Records include materials pertaining to the Chief Executive Officer's office, including minutes, memoranda outlining proposed agendas, reports on past meetings, draft resolutions, studies, correspondence; staff meetings and memoranda (in Box 1, several folders containing Executive Officers Committee material are labeled "EOC"); and long-range planning initiatives. Other major subjects in the collection include investment, athletics, information technology/computing reorganization, land resources, internal audits, policies, budget forecasts, and compensation. A significant part of the collection (found in boxes 3 and 4) includes materials related to discussion in the late 1980s about possible commercial use for part of Duke Forest. Items related to this discussion include land use plans from a variety of institutions; minutes and agenda of Land Resources Committee meetings; letters for and against development of Duke Forest land; report and recommendations of the Land Resources Committee; minutes of the Urban Land Institute presentation to the CEO's of Duke; literature from development companies; and preliminary and final reports and recommendations of the Land Resources Committee. Beginning with Box 4, items are alphabetized; therefore, information related to DUMAC's investment responsibilities are located throughout the subsequent six boxes. Box 11 begins a new accession group-these items are also alphabetized, but are discontinuous with the previous 10 boxes.
Subject Headings
Duke Management Company (DUMAC); Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University -- Finance; Duke University. Athletic Association; Duke University. Athletic Council; Duke Forest (Durham, N.C.); Urban Land Institute; Minutes, Corporate; Law -- North Carolina; Telecommunications; Campus planning
Separated Material
Oversized material related to proposed development of part of Duke Forest was separated out from the main collection and placed in oversize storage.
Related Material
Board of Trustees Records, 1860-2004
Duke University Archives
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - European Special Situations Fund: Report (Box 1)
  - Duke Medical Center Department of Psychiatry Investigative Review, 1990 June (Box 1)
  - EOC Staff Meeting Agendas 1985-1987, 1 of 2 (Box 1)
  - EOC Staff Meeting Agendas 1985-1987, 2 of 2 (Box 1)
  - EOC Memoranda 1985-1987, 1 of 2 (Box 1)
  - EOC Memoranda 1985-1987, 2 of 2 (Box 1)
  - Long-Range Planning Initiatives 1989, 1 of 2 (Box 1)
  - Long-Range Planning Initiatives 1989, 2 of 2 (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1990 June, May, and April (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1990 March (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1990 February (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1990 February (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1990 January (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1989 November-December (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1989 October (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1989 August-September (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1989 June-July (Box 1)
  - CEO Minutes: 1989 April-May (Box 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes: 1989 January-April (Box 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes: 1989 May-December (Box 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes: 1988 January-April (Box 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes: 1988 May-August (Box 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes: 1988 September-December (Box 1)
  - Executive Officers' Retreat, 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 2)
  - Executive Officers' Retreat, 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 2)
  - CEO Minutes, 1988 October 26-November 14 (Box 2)
  - CEO Minutes, 1988 September 29-October 24 (Box 2)
  - CEO Minutes, 1988 September 2-September 27 (Box 2)
  - CEO Minutes, 1988 July and August (Box 2)
  - CEO Minutes, 1988 June (Box 2)
  - CEO Minutes, 1988 May (Box 2)
  - CEO Minutes, 1988 March-April (Box 2)
  - CEO Minutes, 1988 January-February (Box 2)
  - Bankers Trust: SRI Proposal (Bound) (Box 2)
  - Alex Brown and Sons: Senior Underwriting Proposals (Bound) (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Liability Mutual (HELM) Insurance Company: Project Report (Bound) (Box 2)
  - Peat Marwick: Final Report on Acquiring a Telecommunications System, 1985 December (Bound) (Box 2)
  - Quasi and Permanent Endowments, 1990 March 17 (Bound) (Box 2)
  - Telecommunications and Local Area Network (LAN) Task Force Report, 1985 (Bound) (Box 2)
  - University of Virginia: ULI Information Kit (1 of 2) (Box 3)
  - University of Virginia: ULI Information Kit (1 of 2) (Box 3)
  - Letters with No Return Address (Box 3)
  - Duke Forest Development: Letters (1 of 4) (Box 3)
  - Duke Forest Development: Letters (2 of 4) (Box 3)
  - Duke Forest Development: Letters (3 of 4) (Box 3)
  - Duke Forest Development: Letters (4 of 4) (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee Meeting: 1988 June 9 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee Meeting: 1988 May 5 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee Meeting: 1988 April 8 (Box 3)
  - Preliminary Meeting with Wallace, Roberts and Todd: 1988 March 30 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee Meeting: 1988 February 25 (Box 3)
  - Tour of Duke Forest: 1987 December 12 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee Meeting: 1987 November 6 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee: 1987 August 21 (Box 3)
  - Evaluation of Land Use and Development Strategies (Report), 1986 (Box 3)
  - A Guide to Physical Development, UNC-Chapel Hill (Report), 1987 (Box 3)
  - ULI Presentation to Duke CEO, 1986 November 14, 1986 (First Presentation) (Box 3)
  - ULI Presentation to Duke CEO, 1986 November 14 (Second Presentation) (Box 3)
  - ULI Presentation to Board of Trustees: peripheral papers (Box 3)
  - ULI Task Force: Correspondence with Prospective Members, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Report and Recommendations of the Land Resources Committee, 1988 December 12 (Box 3)
  - Urban Land Institute Documents (1 of 2) (Box 3)
  - Urban Land Institute Documents (2 of 2) (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee, 1988 December 8 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee, 1988 November 14 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee, 1988 November 3 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee, 1988 October 11 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee, 1988 September 22 (Box 3)
  - Land Resources Committee, 1988 August 19 (Box 3)
  - Wallace Roberts and Todd, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Report and Recommendations of the Land Resources Committee, 1988 December (Box 3)
  - Engineer's Report on New Parking Areas, Duke University (Box 3)
  - Duke Forest Pamphlet (School of Forestry and Environmental Studies) (Box 3)
  - Duke University Campus Planning Studies (Box 3)
  - Academic Priorities for Duke Forest (Land Resources Academic Subcommittee) (Box 3)
  - Academic Priorities for Duke Forest (draft and final reports) (Box 3)
  - Duke Forest: WRT Working Paper, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Duke University: Briefing Booklet for ULI Study, 1986 November (Box 4)
  - Duke Forest: Working Paper No. 2, 1988 November 3 (Box 4)
  - Duke Forest: Summary WRT Working Paper, 1988 August 19 (Box 4)
  - Decoma Venture (Box 4)
  - Barker Interests Limited (Part of Decoma Venture) (Box 4)
  - Community Concerns Subcommittee: Duke Forest Public Hearing (Box 4)
  - Report and Recommendations of the Land Resources Committee, 1989 February (Box 4)
  - Report of the Community Concerns Subcommittee of the Land Resources Committee, 1988 May (Box 4)
  - Report of the Subcommittee on Non-Academic Uses to the Land Resources Committee, 1988 April 15 (Box 4)
  - Government Officials Meeting, 1988 March 9 (Box 4)
  - Duke Forest Meeting (Box 4)
  - Hammer, Siler, George Associates (Box 4)
  - LRC and Duke Board of Trustees: Introduction to the Duke Forest, 1987 December (Box 4)
  - Growth Management: City, County, State (Box 4)
  - Research Animal Farm, Stadium Drive (Box 4)
  - Duke University's "Accidental" Acquisition of Assets (Draft) (Box 4)
  - Management of the Duke Forest: School of Forestry and Environmental Studies at Duke (Box 4)
  - ULI Pamphlets (Box 4)
  - Value Potential of Non-Campus Lands (Box 4)
  - Law School: Renovation and Addition Plan, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Endowment, 1980 December (Box 4)
  - Sixth Annual Research Triangle Venture Capital Fair, 1989 May (Box 4)
  - Proposal: Advanced Technology Laboratories (Draft), 1987 November (Box 4)
  - Duke University Endowment: Reports, 1981 March, June (Box 4)
  - Duke University Report to Standard and Poor's, 1987 September (1 of 2) (Box 4)
  - Duke University Report to Standard and Poor's, 1987 September (2 of 2) (Box 4)
  - Allen Bldg: Fuller/Dixon Office Space (Box 5)
  - Ambler, Bruce (Box 5)
  - American Industrial Partners (Box 5)
  - Andover Realty (Box 5)
  - NACUBO 1986 Annual Meeting/Seattle, 1986 July 13-16 (Box 5)
  - Arbitrage (Box 5)
  - Arbitration Case: Siecor and Phoenix (Box 5)
  - American Arbitration Association (Box 5)
  - Architect (University) (Box 5)
  - Art Museum (Duke) (Box 5)
  - Athletics: Athletics Policy, 1982 December (Box 5)
  - Athletics: ACC Expansion (Box 5)
  - Athletics at Duke: Philosophy (Falcone Ltr inter alias) (Box 5)
  - Athletic Tickets (Box 5)
  - Ticket Discount (Box 5)
  - ACC Ticket Reduction for Iron Dukes (Box 5)
  - Football, 1990 Fall (Box 5)
  - Bart Koehler: Appeal RE Athletic Scholarship, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Athletics: Jogging Trail, 1989 (Box 5)
  - DUAA: Ruby McLawhon (Box 5)
  - Athletics: Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 5)
  - Concerned "Iron Dukes" (Box 5)
  - Preprofessional Counsel Committee for Athletes (Box 5)
  - Agents for Athletes Interviews, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Athletics: Agent Registration (Box 5)
  - Athletics: Student Mail Openings/J. Potter (Box 5)
  - DUAA Playbook (Box 5)
  - DUAA Administration: Budget (Box 5)
  - DUAA: Reserves and Cap Improvement Plans, 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Athletic Council, Saturday, 1991 February 23 (Box 5)
  - Athletic Council, Alumni House, Saturday, 1990 December 8 (Box 5)
  - Athletic Council, Alumni House, Friday, 1990 September 21 (Box 5)
  - Athletic Council Committee (Box 5)
  - Legislation Committee, Athletic Council (Box 5)
  - Audits, Annual (Box 5)
  - Avanti Investment Advisors (Box 5)
  - Investments: Julius Baer (Box 5)
  - BMR Financial Organization (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Association Investment Committee, 1989 April 28 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee, 1989 February 3 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Association Annual Meeting, 1987 June 18-21 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Board of Governors, 1988 January 22 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee, 1988 January 29 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee, 1988 November 18 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee, 1988 April 29 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee (official letter of Eugene McDonalds' reappointment as Investment Committee Chair), 1989 May (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee: 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Chairman of Bar Investment, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee: Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Phone Conference: 1989 November 10 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Assoc, Board of Governors, 1989 October 5-7 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee Conference Call, 1990 November 2 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee, 1990 August 3 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee Call, 1990 May 3 (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee Meeting, 1990 March 2 (Box 5)
  - Authorization to Sign: Lines of Approval, Authorizing Power, Etc. (Box 5)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee Conference Call, 1991 November 4 (Box 6)
  - NC Bar Investment Committee, 1991 February 1 (Box 6)
  - Benefits Task Force (Box 6)
  - Berg Capital Corporation (Box 6)
  - Bhandari, Ranji (Box 6)
  - Investments: Biocryst (Box 6)
  - Biogen (Box 6)
  - Black Affairs, President's Council on (Box 6)
  - Colin Blaydon (Box 6)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 6)
  - Berko, Malcolm and Freeman, Corinne (Box 6)
  - Brobeck, Phleger and Harrison (Box 6)
  - Brodie Inaugural Address/Speeches (Box 6)
  - Philosophy: Administration (Box 6)
  - Earl Brian (Box 6)
  - Jay Bryan (Box 6)
  - Bryan Neurosciences Building (Box 6)
  - Bryant Electric (Box 6)
  - Buck Consultants (Box 6)
  - Cancer Center: Collaboration with Florida Hospital (Box 6)
  - Canaan Capital (Box 6)
  - Capital Budgeting, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Capital Budgeting - B & F (Box 6)
  - Capital Budgeting, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Funding for Cap Campaign (Box 6)
  - Carolina Cable (Box 6)
  - Investments: Chilmark-Zell (David Schulte) (Box 6)
  - The Christie Report (Box 6)
  - Investments: Clemente Capital (Box 6)
  - Investments: C.L. Global Partners (Box 6)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE) (Box 6)
  - Cohn, Brian, Inc. (Box 6)
  - College Construction Loan Insurance Business (Box 6)
  - Committee of Executive Officers - Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Committee on Facilities and Environment (Box 6)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 6)
  - Compensation Committee (Child Care, Parenting Leave, etc.) (Box 6)
  - Compensation Committee (Box 6)
  - Compensation Committee, 1991 February 21 (Box 6)
  - Compensation Committee, Faculty (Box 6)
  - Basic Sciences Salaries (Box 6)
  - Investments: Constellation Companies (Chris Poindexter) (Box 6)
  - Coopers & Lebrand Study for Johns Hopkins, 1988 August (Box 6)
  - Coopers & Lebrand General Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Cooper, Robertson and Partners (Box 6)
  - Counsel's Office: District Attorney (Box 6)
  - Counsel's Office: General Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Credit Union (Box 6)
  - Debt Financing (Box 6)
  - Depreciation (Box 6)
  - Development: Sharf, Gilbert (Box 6)
  - Development Office: Gifts to Development Officers (Box 6)
  - Deferred Maintenance: Chiller at Broad Street (Box 7)
  - Deferred Maintenance (Box 7)
  - DLTB Real Estate Managers (Box 7)
  - Droege Computing Services, Inc. (Box 7)
  - Duke Eye Center (Box 7)
  - Investments: Electra Investment Trust, plc. (Box 7)
  - Equitable Capital Management Corporation (Box 7)
  - Dober Study (Facility Planning) (Box 7)
  - Duke Childrens School (Box 7)
  - Duke University: Facts and Statistics (Box 7)
  - Early Learning Centre (Box 7)
  - Executive Programs (Box 7)
  - Fuqua Executive Programs (Box 7)
  - Flexible Spending Accounts: General (Box 7)
  - Flexible Spending Accounts: Duke Reimbursement Account (Box 7)
  - Food Lion Proposal (Box 7)
  - Franklin Capital Associates II (Box 7)
  - Fuller, Jon W. (Consortium Advancement Higher Educ.) (Box 7)
  - Robert Gallo, M.D./Organon Laboratory (Box 7)
  - Garda, Robert A. (Box 7)
  - Nathan T. Garrett (Box 7)
  - David J. Greene and Company (Box 7)
  - Field, Ted (Box 7)
  - Forecast: Background, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Forecast: Meeting with Neil Williams, 1989 November (Box 7)
  - Center Forestry Research (Box 7)
  - Duke Forest Advisory Committee (Box 7)
  - Fortsmann-Leff (Box 7)
  - Golf Card International (GCI) (Burr, Egan, Deleage) (Box 7)
  - Greenspring Fund, Inc. (Box 7)
  - Government Relations: State/Local (Box 7)
  - Government Relations: Federal (Box 7)
  - Government Relations: Local/Durham City Council Luncheon, 1990 January (Box 7)
  - Government Relations Office (Box 7)
  - Phillip A. Griffiths (Box 7)
  - Investments: Grubb Properties Inc. (Box 7)
  - Investments: Hambro European Ventures (Box 7)
  - Hanseatic Group, Inc. (Box 7)
  - Harvest Corporate Services (Box 7)
  - Havely Reception (Box 7)
  - Havely, Robert S./EDSOURCE (Box 7)
  - Health Care Oversight Committee (Box 7)
  - Health Insurance Programs: Task Force (Box 7)
  - Henderson Administration Ltd. (Box 7)
  - Henderson Investment Managers (Box 7)
  - Highland Hospital (Box 7)
  - High Point Regional Hospital: Meeting, 1991 November 21 (Box 7)
  - Hooker, Roger W. (Dow, Lohnes and Albertson) (Box 7)
  - Horace Williams Airport (Box 7)
  - Huffman, Ned E. (Box 7)
  - Potential Investments: Oil and Gas (IL Energy Corporation) (Box 7)
  - Infrastructure Material, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Interco (Box 7)
  - Internal Audit (Box 8)
  - Jin Jianrong (Box 8)
  - Johnson, M.B. and J.A. (Box 8)
  - Johnson, Dr. Charles (Retirement Plan Information) (Box 8)
  - Jones, K.C. (Box 8)
  - Sallie Judd (Box 8)
  - Kaludis Report, 1984 December (Box 8)
  - Herbert E. Kann (Box 8)
  - George Kaludis (Box 8)
  - Kaspar, Richard J. (Box 8)
  - Kassko, Inc. (Brian Cohn) (Box 8)
  - Keck Foundation (Box 8)
  - Kelly Endowment (Box 8)
  - LaBoeuf, Lamb Law Firm (Box 8)
  - Investments: Lacey Group (Box 8)
  - Land, Dr. Kenneth C. (Chairman of Sociology) (Box 8)
  - Law School: Addition (Box 8)
  - Lazar, W.R. and Company (Minority-Owned Business) (Box 8)
  - LE Select Investment Partners (Box 8)
  - Lockamy, Dexter (Box 8)
  - Father John LoSchiavo, S.J. (Box 8)
  - Fostin Capital Fund Corp. (Jim Knowles and Tom Levine), 1990 August 2 (Box 8)
  - Steve Kasbeer and Dave Meagher, Loyola University, 1991 March (Box 8)
  - Van Lurton (Box 8)
  - Mackowski, J. Matthew (Box 8)
  - Major Projects Ordinance (Box 8)
  - Management Board (Box 8)
  - Rogers, Casey & Barksdale, Description of Services (Box 8)
  - Mayberry, Odell H. (Box 8)
  - New Management: Philip McCarthy, Jim Weersing (Box 8)
  - Paul MacCowatt Visit, 1985 October 18 (Box 8)
  - Morris McInnes (Box 8)
  - MEDPAC re: DUMAC, 1990 May 7 (Box 8)
  - Medical Science Partners (Harvard) (Box 8)
  - Minority Affairs Officer (Box 8)
  - Dr. Eleanor SMith, Candidate VP Minority Affairs, 1990 March 28 (Box 8)
  - Leonard Beckum, Candidate VP Minority Affairs, 1990 April 20 (Box 8)
  - Minority Affairs: Correspondence, 1989- (Box 8)
  - MLGA Fund I (Box 8)
  - Mobil Oil (Box 8)
  - Morgan Grenfell Capital (Box 8)
  - Morse, Jerry: Talk-a-Walk (Box 8)
  - Daniel P. Moynihan (Box 8)
  - MPC & Associates: Sports/Recreational Facilities (Law School Addition) (Box 8)
  - Housing/Faculty and Staff, MPC & Associates, Inc. (Myron P. Curzan) (Box 8)
  - Golf WDI: Kabon Muto, Ed Ibarguen, Bucky Waters, 1991 April 27 (Box 8)
  - NCAA (Box 8)
  - NCM Capital (Justin F. Beckett) (Box 8)
  - Newby, Melany Stinson (Box 8)
  - New Patriot Fund L.P./"21" International Holdings, Inc. (Box 8)
  - Dinner Honoring Su Ha Newton, 1989 September 12 (Box 8)
  - Meese, Jr., C. James (Princeton Capital Management) (Box 8)
  - O'Herron & Company (Box 8)
  - Oppenheimer Institutional Horizon (Box 8)
  - Overhead as Source of Funds (Box 8)
  - Dinner with His Excellency Turgut Ozal, 1991 March 26 (Box 8)
  - Pacific Century Advisors, 1991 October 14 (Box 8)
  - James K. Parker (Box 8)
  - Pasadena Growth Funds (Box 8)
  - Pascal, Robert Anthony (Box 8)
  - Alan Patricof Associates, Inc. (Box 8)
  - PDC: Leased Employees (Box 8)
  - PDC: Health Service Plan and Agreement with the PDC's (Box 8)
  - Pejacsevich, Peter (Hoare Govett LTD, London) (Box 8)
  - Performance Attribution (Box 9)
  - Petrie Parkman and Company: Direct Investment Energy Seminar (Box 9)
  - Petroleum Funding Corp. (T. Gilliam) (Box 9)
  - Pew Foundation (Box 9)
  - Pictet International (Box 9)
  - Pizzagalli Construction (Box 9)
  - Corporate Planning Office (Box 9)
  - Planning Office: Charge (Box 9)
  - Planning Candidates: John Graham (Box 9)
  - Planning Office Charge Committee (Box 9)
  - PMC Reserve Acquisition Company (Joel Fleishman) (Box 9)
  - Poindexter, Chris (Box 9)
  - Polar-BEK (Box 9)
  - Public Policy Institute: Endowment (Box 9)
  - Policy Sciences: New Building (Box 9)
  - Policy Sciences and Public Affairs Institute (Box 9)
  - Potomac Investment Associates (Box 9)
  - Presidential Retreat, 1989 June 8 (Box 9)
  - Presidential Review Process (Box 9)
  - Investments: Prince Ventures (Box 9)
  - Investments: Provident Capital Management (Box 9)
  - Investments: Proxy Voting (Box 9)
  - Purolator (Investment) (Box 9)
  - Rauch Dinner (Searle Center), 1990 June 20 (Box 9)
  - Rauch Award Dinner (Searle Center), 1988 February 12 (Box 9)
  - Rauch Award Dinner, 1986 December 1 (Box 9)
  - Rauch Award, 1986 February 7 (Box 9)
  - Mediplex Proposal/Crapo's Center (Box 9)
  - Jeff Kurzweil Visit (Box 9)
  - Duke Life Care Center (Box 9)
  - Regis Fund, Inc. (Box 9)
  - Medical Center Process Serving (Box 9)
  - Risk Management: Corporate Negligence (Box 9)
  - Risk Management Office (Box 9)
  - Meador Luncheon, Old Trinity, 1988 May 3 (Box 9)
  - Investments: Rothschild Ventures (Box 9)
  - Russell Robinson, 1989 March 6 (Box 9)
  - Ritchie & Associates (Box 9)
  - Mr. Curtis A. Sampson (Box 9)
  - Dodge NIT BB, Jim Sankovitz Visit, 1990 November 14 (Box 9)
  - Stephen Schwarz (Box 9)
  - Annie Scott, Ph.D, Department of History (Box 9)
  - Sea Level Hospital (Box 9)
  - Sea Level Meeting, 1988 August 11 (Box 9)
  - Scurlock, Mary Christine ("Kiki") (Box 9)
  - Shoup, Paul (Box 9)
  - Dick Siemer (Box 9)
  - Completed Staff Work (Box 9)
  - University Information Systems (Box 9)
  - Simmons, J.T., Lamar Life Insurance (Box 9)
  - Sirgo Production Company (Box 9)
  - Pat Skarulis (Box 9)
  - Synertech Group, Inc. (Box 9)
  - Space Requirements/Duke (Box 9)
  - Spurrier, Stephen (Box 9)
  - Stedman, W. David (Associates)--Rare Coin Investment (Box 9)
  - Stedman, John B. (EJM) (Box 9)
  - Alan Stern (Box 9)
  - Stone, Tom: T.F. Stone Associates (Box 9)
  - Stoughton, M. Vickery (Box 9)
  - Matthew Lind, Robert Meceda, MK, MH, 1991 February 19 (Box 10)